Inventory of the Curtis W. Tarr Papers, 1963-1988
Hoover Institution Archives
Curtis W. Tarr Papers,
1963-1988
74089
Tarr, Curtis W., 1924-
19 manuscript boxes (7.6 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Diaries, memoirs, and printed matter, relating to C. W. Tarr's experience as a soldier in World War II, his public and educational careers, American military and foreign policy and military conscription during the administrations of Presidents Richard M. Nixon and Gerald R. Ford, and the operations of Deere and Company, a multinational corporation.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1974.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
Ford, Gerald R. (Gerald Rudolph), 1913-; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-; United States. Defense Manpower Commission.; United States. Dept. of State.; United States. Dept. of the Air Force.; United States. Selective Service System.; Draft--United States.; United States--Foreign relations.; United States--Armed Forces.; United States--Armed Forces--Recruiting, enlistment, etc.; United States--Foreign relations--1969-1974.; United States--Military policy.
Container List
- Diaries
  - General. Bound volumes of typewritten transcripts
    - 1964 January-1965 June (Box 1)
    - 1965 July-1967 June (Box 2)
    - 1967 July-1968 December (Box 3)
    - 1969 January-1970 June (Box 4)
    - 1970 July-1971 June (Box 5)
    - 1971 July-1972 June (Box 6)
    - 1972 July-1973 June (Box 7)
    - 1973 July-December (Box 8)
    - 1974 January-December (Box 9)
    - 1975 January-1976 June (Box 10)
    - 1976 July-1977 June (Box 11)
    - 1977 July-1978 June (Box 12)
    - 1978 July-1979 December (Box 13)
    - 1980 January-December (Box 14)
    - 1981 January-1982 June (Box 15)
    - 1982 July-1984 June (Box 16)
    - 1984 July-1986 December (Box 17)
    - 1987 January-1988 June (Box 18)
  - Trips. Notebooks
    - Orient, 1970
    - London, 1971
    - Europe, 1971 (Box 19)
    - South East Asia, 1972
- Printed matter